myweather.net 2006-06-15

# MyWeather LLC

**MyWeather LLC**  
**Privacy Policy**

**Effective** **6/30/04** ****

### **Most Recent Revision:  1/31/06**

We take your privacy very seriously.  MyWeather LLC is committed to protecting your privacy while accessing our services or content.  MyWeather is a supplier of content to the web site by which you’re accessing our services, and this policy applies only to content and services supplied and supported directly by MyWeather LLC.  We work hard to integrate our services with our partners’ web sites to give you a great user experience, but such entities are not bound by MyWeather’s privacy policy.  We can therefore make no warranties about the policies governing our partners’ sites in general - please refer to their privacy policy for additional information.

MyWeather, LLC is a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program. TRUSTe is an independent, non-profit organization whose mission is to build users' trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices. This privacy statement covers the site [www.myweather.net](http://www.myweather.net/). Because this web site wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe. 

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact our Privacy Department by email at [privacy@myweather.net](mailto:privacy@myweather.net). If you do not receive acknowledgment of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should then contact TRUSTe [http://truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php](http://truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php) . TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with the Web site to resolve your concerns. 

The TRUSTe program covers only information that is collected through this Web site, and does not cover information that may be collected through software downloaded from the site or information collected by our co-branded partner sites.

**The Information We Collect:**

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on services or content supported by MyWeather LLC. On some pages, you can order products/subscriptions, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages include personally identifiable information (full name, address, email address, phone number, etc.) and demographic information (age, gender, income, hobbies, etc.).  We also collect, store, and use unsolicited information you may provide, such as compliments, complaints, questions, suggestions, and all other communications with us.

All personally identifiable information you provide to MyWeather LLC is stored, whenever possible, in a single personal profile that we establish for you in our database.  When you subscribe to other services provided by MyWeather, we attempt to locate your profile and collect any additional information we may require.  This allows us to provide you with seamless integration between our services.

Most of the information we collect, such as your name, address, and email address, is required in order to provide you with personalized weather or other services for a specific location of interest, such as your home.  Other information is optional, such as your household income level, gender, age, or favorite hobbies.  However, we urge you to provide this information so that we can evolve our services to best match your needs.

Pursuant to the Terms & Conditions of Service for our Personal MicroCast and Desktop Alert services, available to you at no charge, your registration for such products indicates your opt-in to receive MyWeather email notices of product and service updates, enhancements, or new releases.  All communications of this type contain an Internet-based opt-out mechanism that allows you remove yourself from this program.

##  

## Tell-A-Friend: If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend’s name and email address.  We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site.  MyWeather, LLC stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program. 

Your friend may contact us at [privacy@myweather.net](mailto:privacy@myweather.net) to request that we remove this information from our database.

MyWeather and our third party advertisers use Cookies, Web Beacons, and IP Address captures to track usage, behaviors, and other non-Personally identifiable information.

### **Cookies**

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site, and we link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. 

We use persistent cookies to store your passwords, so you don’t have to enter it more than once. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser’s “help” file. Persistent cookies also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site.

If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but you will be asked to log in to access any of our personalized weather services.

This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by [www.myweather.net](http://www.myweather.net/) only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. Some of our business partners (e.g., advertisers) use cookies on our site.  We have no access to or control over these cookies. To learn more about our advertising company’s use of cookies, please email our Privacy Department at [privacy@myweather.net](mailto:privacy@myweather.net).

We employ a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs), that help us track the effectiveness of our content.  Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies.  In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user’s computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on Web pages/emails and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. 

We use clear gifs in our HTML-based emails to let us know which emails have been opened by recipients.  This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of certain communications and the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns.  We tie the information gathered by clear gifs to our customers’ personally identifiable information. If you would like to opt-out of these emails, please see “Choice and Opt-out.” 

** "Wrapped" web pages**

Our web pages are framed by our partner website's content in order to provide you a seamless website experience.  The content on the wrapper is not served by us, and therefore not covered under this privacy policy. 

### **Log Files**

As is true of most Web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files.  This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. 

We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. 

We do not link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information. __

**Payment Processing**

MyWeather uses a third-party payment processor, for our Premium service subscription transactions. All sensitive payment data is collected by MyWeather and sent securely to our billing company for payment processing. Our payment processor can only use your personal information for the purpose of fulfilling payment processing and not for any secondary reasons.

**How We Use Your Information:**

The information may be used in the following ways:

  * We will use it to provide personalized services.  Since our services tend to be customized to the greatest extent possible, nearly all of MyWeather’s services require personally identifiable information in order to provide the personalized information you’ve requested.
  * We may conduct sweepstakes or contests (see “Surveys and Contests” below)
  * We may conduct market research.
  * We may use it to determine which content – weather, news, updates, stories, or other pertinent information – is best to share with you.
  * We may use the information to market to you products and services that may be of interest.
  * We supplement your Personally Identifiable information collected on the site with information from other sources (i.e. your survey responses, etc.).
  * We may publicly use only your first name and last initial (“John D.”) in combination with any feedback you provide, either solicited or unsolicited, to support our marketing and promotion.
  * We may gather and use your Personally Identifiable information to monitor usage, behavior, visit frequency, and other such data.
  * We may combine your Personally Identifiable Information

## Surveys or Contests

From time-to-time your registration with us may provide you the opportunity to participate in contests or surveys via our site or our Television Station partners’ sites. Participation in these surveys or contests is voluntary and you have a choice whether or not your registration is included in promotional activities. 

**How We Share Your Information:**

MyWeather will not sell or otherwise transfer your personally identifiable information to a third party for their sole use.  Your information may be shared with the web site partner by whom you’ve accessed our services upon request for contests or their internal subscriber data.  Information that may be shared include name, email address and street address.  When we share your information, we have agreements with our partners stating that they not sell or transfer your personally identifiable information to third parties.

MyWeather may share your information time to time with reputable third parties, to support basic business functions (“Third Party Processors”).  These Third Party Processors may include, for example, companies that operate our billing and fulfillment functions, or an online store. These Third Party Processors may organize, manage, administer, process, and/or analyze data on our behalf.  Third Party Processors may correct or update such data as needed.  MyWeather will work to ensure that in such arrangements all data is handled securely, and that confidentiality is maintained.

**Other Limitations on Privacy:**

The Personally Identifiable Information you provide us is subject to disclosure (1) pursuant to judicial or other governmental subpoenas, warrants, or orders, (2) where MyWeather LLC believes our property, business, or an individual’s safety or security is at risk, (3) if your actions violate our Terms & Conditions of Service, or (4) if otherwise required by law.

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.   Your personally identifiable information is maintained in a server in a secure co-location facility. Our third-party payment processor uses SSL encryption technology for transaction security.

**How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information: **

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online by visiting a centralized account management page (“Settings”, “Preferences”, etc. depending on the particular MyWeather service). You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error.   To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. 

## Choice/Opt-out

We provide you the opportunity to ‘opt-out’ of having your personally identifiable information used for certain purposes, when we ask for this information.  For example, if you do not wish to be included in promotional activities of the partner offering our weather services, you may opt-out.

If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication or by emailing us at [customerservice@myweather.net](mailto:customerservice@myweather.net). We offer an opportunity to opt-out of certain communications on our “Settings” pages, or you may contact us via mail at the address listed below to opt-out.

**Purchase or** **Sale** **of Business:**

MyWeather LLC may make agreements with other businesses that require the sale or merger of the company.  In such cases, your personally identifiable information is transferable to a different business entity as part of such a deal. You will be notified via prominent notice on our Web site for 30 days of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information.

## Changes in this Privacy Statement

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently.  If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here.

**How To Contact Us: **

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please email us at [privacy@myweather.net](mailto:privacy@myweather.net), or mail us at:

MyWeather LLC

401 Charmany Drive, Suite 200

Madison,  WI 53719

(608) 441-0400
